http://www.olinfrederick.com/privacy-policy

Home/
Print Books/Reducing Global Road Traffic TragediesAs Sick As It GetsThe Waldheim AffairWell-founded Fear
eBooks/Reducing Global Road Traffic Tragedies
About/Mission and ValuesTeamPrivacy Policy
Contact/
Challenging the status quo thinking of selected social and political issues worldwide when realities indicate it needs to be challenged
Privacy Policy
Home/
Print Books/Reducing Global Road Traffic TragediesAs Sick As It GetsThe Waldheim AffairWell-founded Fear
eBooks/Reducing Global Road Traffic Tragedies
About/Mission and ValuesTeamPrivacy Policy
Contact/
Your privacy is important to us and Olin Frederick Publishing, Inc. is committed to protecting it. We collect certain types of information about visitors to our website. Below is an explanation about the types of information we gather and what we do with it.Information CollectedOlin Frederick Publishing collects identifying information from users: personal data (such as names and e-mail addresses); and aggregated data such as information about traffic patterns on our website.Privacy PolicyPersonal data is collected when users voluntarily provide such information to Olin Frederick Publishing, for example in registering for electronic newsletters, purchasing items, and registering for other promotional opportunities. We will not use your personal data for any purpose other than as stated, and will not sell or rent your name or address to any third parties whatsoever.Aggregated InformationAggregated information, such as which pages users access or visit and information volunteered by users, such as survey information and/or site registrations, is collected through various methods. For example, Olin Frederick Publishing collects IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the internet. Web servers, the computers that host websites, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from OlinFrederickPublishing.com, our servers log your IP address. OlinFrederickPublishing.com does not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to us.OlinFrederickPublishing.com also uses cookies to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit them. Cookies allow OlinFrederickPublishing.com to measure activity on our website to improve your user experience. Cookies are used by OlinFrederickPublishing.com to measure activity on our websites to make improvements and updates based on which areas are popular and which are not. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except for personal information voluntarily provided by you, OlinFrederickPublishing.com does not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever.Use of CookiesUse of InformationOlinFrederickPublishing.com uses both the personal and aggregated information we collect for multiple purposes. The information is used to improve content on our website, to customize the content and/or layout of our website for each individual user and to notify users about website updates or promotional offers or announcements we believe will be of interest to you.Olin Frederick Publishing may also share information if such information is subpoenaed, or if Olin Frederick Publishing believes that any user has committed unlawful acts, to acts that endanger the health or safety of another user or of the general public. In some situations, we will share your personal information, on a confidential basis, with third parties who perform a particular service on our behalf, such as sending e-mails or processing credit card payments.It is important to note that OlinFrederickPublishing.com may contain links to external websites and that these sites may not follow the same privacy policies as OlinFrederickPublishing.com.Links to Other SitesAdditional InformationNo transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of OlinFrederickPublishing.com to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, Olin Frederick Publishing cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.Under no circumstances, including but not limited to negligence, shall Olin Frederick Publishing be liable for any special, incidental or consequential damages that result from the use of information or materials on our website, even if Olin Frederick Publishing has been advised of the possibility of such damages.By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Your ConsentIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on December 26, 2016.Contacting Us:If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below or via our Contact form here.Olin Frederick Publishing, Inc.PO Box 200Margaretville, NY 12455Email: info@OlinFrederick.comTel: +1 845-243-3219Changes to our Privacy Policy
HomeTeamContactPrivacy Policy
© Copyright Olin Frederick Publishing, Inc. 2014-2019
